I look up to the stars and reach for
the sky I believe in tomorrow if we try!
Hey!
Come on, let's go, everybody.
Oh, we share the music.
We share the music.
Come on, let's go, baby, baby.
Oh, we share the one dream.
Come on, let's go, everybody.
Oh, we share the good times.
We share the good times.
Come on, let's go.
Baby, baby, oh, we share the one world.
It's hard to see for you and me.
Through the darkness
that is in this world.
So hard to see or to believe.
In where we need to go.
Yes, you and me, it's true that we.
Feel the rush brought up by this world.
Through head to feet, I feel the beat.
Getting me to walk on, oh yeah.
Share the music, no matter what.
Share the one dream, believe in yourself.
Share the good times, take my hand now.
Share the one world now.
I look up to the stars
and reach for the sky.
No matter what, I'll
try no matter how high.
So let us go beyond, far and wide.
I believe in tomorrow if we try.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on, let's go, everybody.
Oh, we share the music.
We share the music.
Come on, let's go, baby, baby.
Oh, we share the one world. No!
Oh, as we chase, we're being chased.
From the top we go on straight and wild.
We're on our way, I've got to say.
Hey, I want to share your style.
Now here it starts, so don't lose heart.
They're bound to lose to this flavor.
From boot to hood, I feel so good.
I will be free to be, oh yeah.
Share the music, even if I.
Share the one dream, I know where you are.
Share the good times,
share the one world now.
I look up to the stars.
And reach for the sky.
No matter what.
I'll try no matter how high.
So let us go.
Beyond, far and wide.
I believe in tomorrow.
If we try.
I know that you are there.
Just on the other side.
Wait there for me.
Soon it will be you and I.
Then let us go.
Beyond, far and wide.
I believe in the one world.
If we try.
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah.
Come on let's go everybody.
Oh we share the music.
Oh come on let's go. Maybe maybe.
Oh we share the one world.
Damn, this guy's unreal.
He can shoot those beams
from his hands and his mouth
How's he shooting us with anyway
beings obviously that would be pretty
kick-ass if it were true that tech
doesn't even exist It's just fantasy way.
What are you doing over there?
I'm playing dead. See?
That's not true
Style all right now come
come about some Diable
Yes, way to go!
They took him down!
Those three are just too awesome!
Don't forget he's one of the warlords.
It'll take a lot more
than that to beat him.
And judging by their
faces, they know that too.
So he's different now?
Well, then maybe he's a twin or something.
It's possible, but that's a scary thought.
They look the same, but they're different.
The real one when they
teleported to dodge our attacks.
And he doesn't use that shockwave attack.
He doesn't have those paws either.
Well, he's plenty strong as is.
And what's worse, the real
one might be after us as well.
well done you gave me quite a beating but
I'm not just bigger now I'm much Stronger,
too, than Trabucin!
The mad monk, Rouge,
may have escaped death countless
times before reaching this place.
But no matter how strong he
grows, he cannot escape his fate.
It burns!
That was Kizuru's laser.
So he recreated Kizuru's attacks
while using Bartholomew Kuma's body?
Damn that Vegapunk.
I had no idea the pacifista
technology had advanced so quickly.
It's one hell of a show!
You've got to admit that.
Indeed.
But a warlord and an admiral friend?
Not even three pirates with bounties
over a hundred million can handle that
Is that rear admiral Drake?
Sorry, former rear admiral.
Not here for your old job back, I take it?
Or perhaps you'd like
to test the pacifista?
I'm afraid your inside knowledge will
only make your despair all the greater.
Also, I suggest you, little chickies,
exercise the level of caution.
After all, you have me
to contend with, too.
Damn, this fight just delivers
one crazy thing after another!
It's a rare ancient Zolan type!
I've never seen one before!
Oh, my God.
Imagine that.
You bleed red blood just
like the rest of us.
I'm surprised.
A truly rare sight.
I'm speechless.
As I was just saying, you
have to contend with me, too.
Uh, uh?
Huh, now ain't that something you
supernovas are a strange bunch?
Every one of you turns
into some scary monster!
Demon face
He's gone
My eyes Captain Hawkins,
run, get out of there!
I can see?
I don't know what your power is, but
I do know you have a physical form.
It doesn't seem like you're a Logia-type.
Captain Hawkins!
He doesn't have any more
voodoo dials to protect him.
He can't take any more of this.
Looks like you're the first to go.
You did well to journey all this way,
and for that, you have my compliments.
Huh?
Yo!
Yo,
yo, yo, yo, yeah, yo, is
this music reaching you?
If you can hear it, stay
tuned, Navy Admiral Kizaru.
So he's the one, he's the sea roar.
Here's the Dial, fighting
music, kicking it live.
Come on, scratch.
What is this all about?
Here we go!
Check it out!
Though knowing you navy admirals you'll
probably be right back up in a second
Glad I hung around for a
bit this was a sight to
see I guess it's time
for me to scram Peace out
How terrible
That was quite a shock.
I'll use the Yata mirror
Oh, my God.
So, let's go.
Oh, ah, here it is.
This is Barcelona.
Ah, what the heck, Uncle?
You do have a baby transponder snail.
Why didn't you contact me? Huh?
Oh, is that you sent to Moria?
Don't give me that is that you business.
Where are you?
What are you doing?
I tried contacting you before,
but I couldn't get a hold of you.
Don't tell me you were trying to talk
into the black transponder snail again.
Huh?
I've told you before, the black one on
your wrist is for eavesdropping, remember?
Oh, that's right.
Ugh, it's fine. Forget it.
It's time we get to work now.
It seems the culprits have split up.
Straw Hat Luffy, Captain
Eustass Kidd, and Trafalgar Law.
Which one do we start with?
Huh, split up.
In that case, well...
Zoro!
Hey, Zoro, what's the matter with you?
How are you already hurt so bad?
We just started.
Look, just forget about
him for now, Luffy.
We're all screwed if we
can't beat this thing.
Yeah, right.
He hasn't had the chance to recover
from last time standing up to
him at all must be pretty damn
painful that look on his face tells me
everything i need to know this
bastard wants us dead but if he's not
bartholomew kuma who the hell is he
either way we don't have time for this
If we don't get out of here we're gonna
be even worse off than we are now?
Let's drop hammer!
Franky Boxing!
Spider-neck!
Hey, you don't need to punch so hard!
The lasers are enough!
Good luck dodging this!
I dare say you're in
for it. Here it comes.
Swallow, bone devil!
Ah! I'm stuck!
That was not my plan!
Hold on! No!
Please, sir, let's be
reasonable about this!
I'd rather you not kill me right now!
Although, you know, I
am already dead, but...
I feel like that's the size of mine!
This special attack happens! Dumb it!
Now's our chance!
Run like hell!
I was terrified!
I didn't think I could pick you enough!
Huh?
Hey, check it out! He's down!
What the?
Wait, so explosives work
on him all of a sudden?
It sank one of them into his mouth.
It must have shorted out
something inside of him
His body may be hard as steel,
but his skin still bleeds.
He's just like me.
He's got a normal old human body It's
been modified and stuffed full of weapons
Nami! Look out!
He's got a lock on you!
Holy crap!
Ochenta fleur!
Squat Romano!
And shock.
Nice one!
Who needs to fight when we can
just make him blow himself up?
We should have thought of this before!
Hey, you might want to sit somewhere else.
That spot is under a storm warning.
From the dark clouds to my slime attack.
Thunderbolt! Tits out!
So, did it work or not?
That attack didn't blow him down at all!
The only thing it did is piss him off!
Desperation's the same as
admitting you've lost the fight.
Hey, knock his ass over here.
Gotta have a piece of the action, huh?
Diable chambe!
Flambe shot!
Nice!
We're finally starting to wear him down!
Demon aura!
Nine sword style!
As my vision board!
So many sorrows!
Nine lightning strikes!
You're near!
Here goes!
Luffy, smash him!
Just one last push!
Go, go!
Luffy, go!
I am my fault!
I'm Shrinky!
That dude?
Is he done?
Seems like it. About time.
Jeez he looks fine creepy.
If he's fine then we are
screwed i'm too tired
to move anymore you know
maybe we should have run.
Instead of fighting no
it's best to take them
on as they come one at a
time we're being chased.
We can't get cornered true
but still he wasn't kuma who
was he we know he's a cyborg
so he must have been a person
at some point but if this guy
isn't the real bartholomew
kuma then why the heck does he
look just like him maybe the
guy's got a twin if not they
must have modified the crap
out of him to make him look
the same can't imagine why
though he couldn't have been
created from scratch you can't
do that with a living person
tx4
we need to get some rest.
I was up for a fight, but that
guy was way too much for me.
I'm exhausted.
A break would be nice, but we've
got to find a place to hide first.
If they find us now, there's
no way we can fight them off.
Yeah, I know.
But let's just sit here for a few minutes.
You guys got some real nerve.
Look what you've done.
What the? Another enemy? Where is he?
There he is! Up there! Huh?
House!
Who are you?
I'm disgusted.
You're an utter disgrace, PX4.
The Navy's not made of money.
Building just one of you pacifistas
costs as much as an entire warship.
Seriously, you know how this is going to
look in my report to that lousy Vega Puck?
Is that another one right with him?
Are you kidding me?
Is that the real one?
Does it really matter if
it's the real one or not?
We've already gotten a taste
of how strong the fakes are.
We can't take another fight, not with him.
Wait, pacifista?
Yeah, that's what he called him.
He didn't seem like much
of a pacifist, though.
So, you think that's
his name or something?
All right, axe boy, just
who the hell are you?
I've got an identity
outside of my axe, you know.
And there's no point in asking questions.
I have no reason to answer you.
I am the most well-guarded
and tight-lipped man alive.
Nobody can break down my
impenetrable defenses.
Oh, come on.
You can at least tell us your name.
Did you hear a single
thing I just told you?
My lips are sealed. Trust me.
There's not one person
more secretive than me.
Saint Moria.
Gotcha.
So you're Saint Moria.
Uh, to be clear, I
wanted you to know that.
That's why I told you.
And not because you wanted to know, okay?
PX1, let's get started.
Still no problems this
guy shoots beams from
his hands too starting to
look like they've got a
whole army of these guys
what is this crap i'm
more concerned staying
alive the mystery can wait?
We're too worn down there's just no way
we can make it through another fight!
When we haven't even met the admiral yeah.
We can't win, let's run, but not
all together, we need to split up.
Sounds good to me, run!
We're the toughest, we'll
each lead our own group.
Right, are you gonna be okay on your own?
Hey, shut up!
Wait up, Knife!
We should stick together!
I'll protect you no matter what, even
if it means sacrificing my life! Thanks!
Thanks!
Now, Red, faster!
If you're really willing
to sacrifice yourself,
why don't you hang back
and act as a decoy?
It's a ladies-only offer, idiot.
You can take care of your
own damn self, Panty Man.
Dorry!
Don't let me die!
Protect me with all your might, okay?
You suck!
I'm already in enough pain as it is!
Fret not, my friend.
I'll proudly supply the
strength you currently lack.
I can only imagine how much
healing you've left to do.
I happened to witness your act
of selfless bravery on Thriller
Bark when you offered your
own life in place of Luffy's.
All right. Thanks.
Up there! Head that way! Got it.
No more laser things! Hey! Guys!
Meet back on the Sony in three days!
They're splitting into groups!
Go after them, Pucci!
Make sure you don't let
him out of Grove 12.
We don't need that headache.
Special attack.
Super Smoke Star.
Now's our chance. Run for it.
You really are quite dependable.
He took out the bridge.
Here he comes.
No.
Why is he apparized?
Look, I don't know, but
will you quit pushing me?
I should have to go to the house.
He's over there.
Are you guys okay?
I'd worry about myself if I were you.
I've got no grudge against you
pirates, but a job is a job.
Now, come go!
Got me!
What the? What?
How do you even do that?
Your offensive skills are impressive,
but they're useless against my defense.
Has she got a good point job?
Luffy!
Hopefully, this guy is strong!
Just so you know, I don't
even have Devil Fruit powers!
That makes it worse.
Man, this is weird. Zoro!
Who?
Who are you?
What are you? Whatever!
Just get the hell away from Zoro!
Oh, no, no, Zoro!
He got hit by one of those laser beams!
Hang in there, buddy!
Come on!
It's about time you got here.
Took you long enough, Uncle Kizaru.
Kizaru? Hey, Usopp! Be careful!
That man's a Navy Admiral!
An Admiral!
Uh-oh!
Your time is up, Pirate Hunter Zoro.
Last I checked, you had 120 million bounty,
so this is not what I was expecting.
Your reputation as a swordsman is known
far and wide, but one hit and you're down?
That's a real shame, ain't it?
You must be pretty worn out, hmm?
Damn.
They have not found us.
Well, you'll have plenty
of time to rest up now.
Zoro!
Crap!
He shoots beams too?
How are we supposed to beat these guys?
At point blank like that, he's done for!
Zoro's in trouble!
Come on, do something, guys!
Get away from him!
Back up or else! Take this!
What? What the hell? Why?
What is this? What's happening?
I can't hit him!
I can't stab him! What the?
What can we do? Trying! Dammit!
Move your foot! I mean it!
Leave him alone!
Step away from our friend!
You're wasting your time.
I ate the glint glint fruit
and now I'm made of light.
It's a Logia, you see.
He's made of light?
This is a nightmare.
There's nothing we can do.
Zoro!
Try to run away! Hurry!
I can't move.
I'm too weak.
It's no use.
The bastard's worn out.
He can't save himself.
Now, Vantek, look!
Yes!
Awesome work, Robin!
He just shifted in place! Unbelievable!
It's cute how your friends want to save
you, But you're far beyond help now.
Well then, time to die.
You picked some time
to come out of hiding.
You sure you want to do
this, Dark King Rayleigh?
Don't go picking these
buds before they sprout.
Their era is only just beginning, and
I want to see what they do with it.
Rayleigh!
The geezer saved Zoro!